NETFLIX PRESENTS
[ woman ] Do you ...
Do you believe in such things as blessings ?
Say , for instance , wishing on your birthday ,
or wishing someone safe travels ,
or maybe even , wishing Merry Christmas , or the like .
It may be just a thought
or perhaps even a reminder .
The fact is , involuntarily and quite unconsciously ,
we believe our will can bring about good outcomes .
But do you know that your will can actually change the outcomes of events ?
Let 's do an experiment now .
Please use your mind to move the rotation of the Ferris wheel to the right .
Now to the left .
To the left .
To the right .
- To the right . - [ train chugs ]
The direction of this moving train
can also be either moving forward or backward based on your will .
Now I want you to try to control it only with your mind .
Did you see that ?
Our will is quietly shaping this world .
This is how blessings work .
[ indistinct chants ]
My name is Li Ronan .
Six years ago , I violated a terrifying taboo .
Back then , anyone fortunate enough to come close to this matter ,
was befallen with misfortunes I can 't explain .
MOM AND DAD.MP4
[ mom ] What deity are you talking about ?
Did you watch what 's on that camera ?
Didn 't the master instruct us
- not to listen , look , and ask anything ? - [ dad ] Master , master , please .
- And you kept asking questions . - You have to believe everything he says ?
- [ tires screeching , crashing ] - [ mom screams ]
And with this curse ,
the more you understand it , the more you 'd be affected by its power .
- I am Li Kuo-sheng . - [ trunk horn honks , thuds ]
No ! [ screams ]
[ inaudible dialog ]
[ gunshot ]
- [ gunshot ] - [ video whizzing ]
I actually made this video because ,
I 'm hoping that everyone can help resolve my daughter 's misfortune .
If you 're willing to keep watching ,
just in case you 'll be able to help ,
please look at this symbol until ,
until you 've memorized it .
[ indistinct chanting ]
[ Ronan ] Ten .
Nine .
Eight .
Seven .
Six .
Five .
Four .
Three .
Two .
One .
And if you can ,
please recite this with me .
Doing it in your mind is fine too .
HOU-HO-XIU-YI , SI-SEI-WU-MA
[ in Yunnan dialect ] Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
[ in English ] Hi , Dodo .
Hello , Dodo .
Hi-lo , Dodo .
Uh , hello , this here is a new camera I bought
- I ... - [ doorbell rings ]
Oh , this is not bad at all .
It 's better than I expected .
- Here , good job . - [ chuckling ]
Hey , congratulations .
You can finally bring Dodo home next week .
[ chuckles ] Thanks so much .
[ Ms. Hsia ] What are you filming ?
[ Ronan ] Oh , it 's nothing .
I just want to record the time that Dodo is here .
And maybe turn it into a sort of diary documenting her new life .
Aah .
Listen , I hope you don 't think I 'm being nosy .
I know that you 're Dodo 's mother .
But if you don 't pass the evaluation period ,
it 's unlikely that the court will grant you custody .
And besides , you still have that record from your past .
[ sighs ] Don 't worry , I 'll cooperate .
You better do that .
Oh , wait . How do I turn this on ?
Oh , uh ... you didn 't switch it off before , so you can just keep filming .
Why aren 't you smiling ?
[ exhales ] Come on over here .
Take a peek , come on , see . There .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Okay , I can film from here .
Why don 't you go in and play with them ? Give that to me .
Okay , I 'll go in first then .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Yes , go ahead .
- [ Ronan ] Hello . - [ man ] Oh , hi , hi . Hello there .
Ronan ?
Yeah , that 's right , I 'm Ronan .
[ chuckles ] Come on . Why don 't you stand up ,
- Dodo and greet your mom ? - Hi .
I 'm Ming , hello .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Have you heard of the New Life Diary before ?
" New Life Diary " ?
You see , um ...
I 'm just filming this as a memento .
Um , hey Dodo , say hi to your mom . Come on .
It 's ... It 's okay . This ...
This is for you .
Wow ! Go ahead and say thank you , Dodo .
- Thank you , thank you so much . - [ Ronan ] No ...
Let me go over there .
This lighting is good .
So , we 're recording a " New Life Diary " for Dodo .
[ Ronan ] Yes , as a memento .
Ah , right .
- Okay . All right . - [ Ronan ] Okay .
Why do you want to run a foster home ?
I never really thought about it .
Well , perhaps ...
Perhaps it 's to um ...
Mm ... [ clicks tongue ]
Perhaps it 's because I 've always wanted to know what being a father feels like .
- [ Ronan ] I see . - Mm .
- Do you want to bring me there ? - Yes , that 's right . Come on , let 's go .
- Okay . - Come on , come on .
Ms. Hsia , how much of this will you be filming ?
- So , you ... - [ Ms. Hsia ] Until the battery runs out .
[ Ming ] Is that your camera , Ronan ?
Yes , I just bought it .
Aah .
[ exhales ] Um , Dodo .
Is this your favorite toy , huh ?
Mm-hm .
- Wow . And what 's its name ? - [ Ming ] Mm .
Woofy .
- [ Ming ] Sit properly , Dodo . Mm . - [ Ms. Hsia ] Dodo , sit up .
Mommy , is it okay if we take Woofy home with us ?
[ Ronan ] Mm ...
- Sure , yes . - Hey , Dodo .
Listen to me .
Let 's keep Woofy here , is that okay ?
Because we have to keep him here for the other kids .
But this is daddy 's promise .
I promise , that we will keep looking for new Woofies .
Okay ?
Do we have a deal ? Hmm ?
[ Ming imitates dog barking ]
[ Dodo imitates dog barking ]
[ imitates dog barking ]
[ both imitate dog barking ]
So , do we have a deal ?
- Let 's see it . - [ whines ]
She 's different .
Dodo is special .
She would call me Daddy .
The other kids don 't do that .
SIX YEARS AGO
[ doctor ] Miss Li Ronan .
I 'd like to inform you that for follow-up purposes ,
we will be recording this session .
[ Ronan ] Sure .
FOOTAGE FROM DR. WU NEW-EAST MENTAL INSTITUTION
Okay .
[ Dr. Wu ] So , you think that this um ... " tunnel that you must not enter "
has brought misfortune to those around you .
Is that right ?
Yes .
[ Dr. Wu ] Then based on what you 're saying ,
did the baby you were carrying ...
die ?
I gave her away .
[ Dr. Wu ] I 'm just a little curious . Can you explain
why nothing has happened to you and your baby ?
Because I remember you mentioned before
that knowing too much would bring certain misfortune .
Yes .
[ Dr. Wu ] And you 'll die if you answer your name .
Even just watching the video filmed inside this tunnel
would kill you .
All I know about ...
about this deity ...
[ in strained voice ] ... is that the more you understand about it ,
the more likely you 'll encounter misfortune .
[ sniffling ]
[ whimpers ]
[ sobbing ]
[ camera beeps ]
Huh ?
Ooh ...
Come ...
[ camera beeps ]
- I feel embarrassed because ... - [ Ming chuckles ]
- ... there 's so many of you . - [ Ming ] It 's fine .
- [ Ms. Hsia ] It 's okay . - [ woman ] Don 't worry .
Is the watermelon sweet ?
[ all ] Yes !
[ man ] Is this a photo or video ?
- Oh , is that it ? - The setting is wrong ?
- [ Ming ] You 're moving to a new home . - [ Ms. Hsia ] Be careful , all right .
The ... the key .
- [ Ms. Hsia ] Hey , what 's wrong ? - Do you have it , Ms. Li ?
- [ Ming ] Do you have the key ? - [ Ronan ] Yes , but I didn 't lock it .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Bye-bye .
- [ Ming ] Let me take a look . - No , there 's no need .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Oh , you 're unbelievable . Really .
It 's okay , it 's here . It 's in the car .
- [ Ms. Hsia ] You 're so forgetful . - [ coughs ]
It 's okay , don 't worry .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Always listen to your mom , okay ?
- Okay , I will . - [ Ms. Hsia ] Okay . Very good .
- Are you ready ? Here we go ! - [ Ming ] Behave , okay .
- Bye ! - [ Ming ] Goodbye !
- Drive safely . - [ Ronan ] Okay .
[ Ms. Hsia ] Oh , hold on .
Hey .
What ?
Aren 't you forgetting something important ?
- Ms. Hsia , thank you so much . Thank you . - [ Ms. Hsia sighs ]
There 's a bread store right over there .
Is there a kind of bread that you like eating , huh ?
Um ...
Dodo , do you like eating bread ?
I like everything .
Yeah ?
You like everything ? That 's great .
Hello there . Today is the first day in our new home .
[ Ronan exhales ] Let me .
You have to flip it around , like so .
Can you see me now ?
Yeah ?
And this here is your room .
Ta-da !
[ chuckles ] Do you like it ?
Mommy , why are we filming all of this ?
Oh ...
Because , you know Mommy used to be sick and I couldn 't look after you .
But now that I 'm fine and well , we can finally be together .
That 's why I want to record this
so we can watch it together when you grow up .
Okay ?
Okay .
All right .
How about I teach you how to write your name ?
- Mm . - Let 's write a very fat name .
- Okay ! - Okay .
[ giggles ]
Chen ...
Le ...
Tung .
Okay . Come on .
Let 's show it to the camera .
See this right here , that 's Dodo 's full name .
- Read it with me . Okay ? - Mm .
" Chen Le-tung . "
Okay , good . Let 's read it again using a fat voice .
- " Chen Le-tung . " - " Chen Le-tung . "
- [ both laughing ] - [ glass breaking ]
Wait here , okay ? Don 't go anywhere .
[ clicks ]
[ tick-tock ]
[ eerie music ]
[ Ronan sighs ]
[ exhales ]
- [ grunts ] - [ Ronan ] Did I touch your eye ?
Did I ? Does it hurt ?
Yes , that 's right , look up . [ sighs ]
What 's this ?
Today is the very first day of Dodo staying in our new home .
She just fell asleep .
She smiled at me today .
So , I feel like I must have done pretty well .
- Well , at least I hope I did . - [ circuit breaks ]
- [ Ronan grunts ] - [ clicks ]
[ tacks ]
[ groans ]
[ exhales ]
[ sighs ]
[ rattling ]
[ Ronan ] Hmm ?
[ refrigerator rumbles ]
[ drips ]
[ sighs ]
[ gasps ]
[ thuds ]
[ light switches on and off ]
Is anybody there ?
[ light continues switching on and off ]
[ whimpers ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ eerie music ]
[ shaky breathing ]
[ light continues switching on and off ]
- [ woman crying ] - [ Ronan gasps ]
[ woman crying continues ]
- [ woman wails ] - [ gasping ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ panting ]
[ clanks ]
- [ creaks ] - [ gasps ]
Dodo .
[ panting ]
[ toilet flushing ]
[ gasping ]
Dodo ?
- [ heavy breathing ] - [ Dodo giggles ]
- Dodo ! - [ snarls ]
Dodo ?
[ Dodo ] Chen Le-tung .
Chen Le-tung .
Dodo .
- Do ... - [ snarls ]
Chen Le-tung ...
Chen Le-tung .
- [ snarling , shrieks ] - [ banging ]
[ shrieking ]
Dodo !
Dodo ! Dodo .
- [ shrieking continues ] - Dodo , Dodo , what 's the matter ?
Dodo , Dodo , look at me . Dodo . Look at me , Dodo !
[ Ronan ] Dodo !
Dodo , it 's okay . I 'm here , Dodo .
Mommy 's here , you 're safe .
It 's all right , I 'm here .
GHOST BUSTERS ( SIX YEARS AGO )
[ Ronan ] What are you doing ?
You look so ugly .
Up yours . Hmm .
45 % COMPLETE STRANGE MURMURS CHANNEL
Hi and welcome to the Strange Murmurs Channel .
I 'm Yuan .
Um ... my name is Ronan .
He 's Dom , an NTU student .
He 's Dom .
And we are now driving on a strange mountain .
And currently , there is no phone signal at all .
[ Dom ] How can the " tunnel you must not enter " have a phone signal ?
Are you serious ?
- Okay then . - [ Dom sighs ]
In this episode , we , the Ghost Busters ,
will take all of you to see , the tunnel that has no phone signal
at all and must not be entered .
So , loyal viewers .
Are you ready to bust this superstition with us ?
- [ both ] Go ! - Go !
- [ engine sputters ] - Aah !
- What 's the matter ? - What happened ?
[ Dom ] Fuck !
[ Dom ] Fuck , what the hell is this ?
[ Yuan ] Huh ?
Do you see it ?
[ Yuan ] Oh , fuck .
What the hell is this ?
What is this ?
A Buddha statue ?
Looks like it .
What did you say Granduncle and the others worship ?
Uh ... I think they worship ...
A Mother-Buddha or celestial being or something . I don 't really know .
[ Yuan ] Mother-Buddha ? It 's female ?
[ Ronan retching ]
[ Yuan ] What 's wrong ?
- [ Dom ] Are you okay ? - [ Yuan ] She 's possessed .
- [ retching continues ] - [ Yuan ] Has it started ?
- [ Dom ] Shut up . - [ Yuan ] Has it started so soon ?
- [ Dom ] Are you okay ? - [ Yuan ] Hey viewers , take a look !
- [ coughs ] - She 's being possessed live on camera .
- Tell us how you feel . - You 're so annoying !
[ retches , vomits ]
Fuck ! That 's a lot .
- [ Ronan ] Ooh . - [ Yuan ] Careful , bro .
- [ Dom ] Don 't worry , it 's fine . - [ gate creaks ]
[ Yuan ] Is that Granduncle ?
[ Dom ] Yeah .
[ electronic window whirs ]
A-Dom , A-Yuan .
- [ Yuan ] Granduncle . - Long time no see . You 're both so big now .
[ all chuckling ]
- This isn 't easy to find , right ? - [ Dom ] Yeah , very difficult .
And this is ?
She 's not from our family , right ?
[ Dom ] No , she 's not .
- A-Yuan . - [ Yuan ] Hmm ?
What are you filming ?
Oh , no , nothing , it 's a toy .
See , I just bought it .
I might not have been clear with you on the phone .
- This is a private family ritual . - [ grunts ]
We do not allow outsiders to participate .
But Granduncle , she 's not an outsider .
She 's his girlfriend .
- [ Dom ] Yes , that 's right . - I 'm his girlfriend .
[ laughing ]
Ah , miss . Do you know how to drive ?
Maybe you can just come back
after we 're finished .
- Huh ? - What do you mean ?
[ Ronan ] I 've never driven alone before .
You can work it out amongst yourselves .
You want her to drive down by herself , Granduncle ?
- Uh , hey , wait . Uh ... - [ Yuan ] Who 's this old woman ?
What is she doing ? Why does she keep staring at me ?
- [ Yuan ] I don 't know . Who is she ? - [ Dom ] What 's going on right now ?
[ Yuan ] Who is she ?
[ Ronan ] I told you to ask , but you wouldn 't . Now , look .
[ Dom ] How would I know ?
Granduncle .
Ah , miss , if you don 't mind .
Can we take a look at your hand ?
- [ Dom ] Her hand ? - My hand ?
- You must be tired after all that driving . - [ Dom ] I 'm exhausted .
Go take a shower . It 's your first time . You can worship first .
[ Dom ] So early ?
Didn 't you say we 'll do it in the middle of the night ?
[ Granduncle ] We have to pray again later .
- A-Dom , listen . - [ Dom ] Yeah ?
[ Granduncle ] The one who felt your girlfriend 's hand just now
is the Chen family 's most senior Great-aunt .
[ Dom ] Aah ...
- [ Yuan ] I 'm sorry . - [ Granduncle ] She always going on
- about Su-e 's two sons . - [ Yuan chuckles ]
- [ Granduncle ] Great-aunt is over there . - [ Dom ] Okay .
Great-aunt .
[ Granduncle ] These are Su-e 's sons .
[ Yuan laughing ]
[ Granduncle ] The most handsome ones in the Chen family .
- [ Ronan ] How are you , Great-aunt ? - [ Granduncle ] Greet your Great-aunt .
A-Yuan , what are you doing ? What is there to film at home ?
[ Yuan ] Oh , it 's nothing .
Granduncle , isn 't that a tunnel over there ?
Ah , you . Listen to me . We 're here to worship , not play around .
- Hey , which brand is this , huh ? - [ Ronan ] Hmm ?
It 's so amazing .
[ Ronan ] What do you mean ?
- Even my nose looks sharper . - [ Ronan sighs ]
[ Ronan ] All done .
What 's it like to have your daughter back ?
Pretty good . It 's all going well .
[ colleague ] Hey . What are these ?
Bugs ?
[ Ronan ] Will you stop messing around ? Come here and get to work .
[ colleague ] There are bugs here . Look , they 're all over .
What are you ... [ gasping ]
[ colleague ] Hey . The bag ! They 're inside the bag .
That 's so gross .
- [ colleague grunts ] - [ Ronan groans ]
[ colleague ] Oh , gross .
- It 's on your shirt ! - Where is it ? Where is it !
- [ colleague ] Right there , do you see it ? - [ yells ]
[ Ronan groans ]
- [ phone rings ] - [ colleague ] Oh , no . You crushed it .
- Hello ? - That 's dirty . How gross !
Yes , right , this is she .
Um ...
Oh , hi . Hello , ma 'am .
[ sighs ]
- Where ? Where does it hurt ? - [ Ming ] Dodo .
- Come on , tell me . - [ Ming ] Come out .
- Okay , Dodo ? Come , apologize to him . - [ man ] Chang Che-wei , what 's the matter ?
- Apply some medicine for him , okay ? - It 's okay . It 's okay , it 's fine now .
- [ teacher ] Let 's put medicine on it . - [ Ming ] Come on , Dodo .
- [ Dodo grunts ] - [ man ] Dodo .
[ Ming ] Come on .
Oh dear , watch your head . Where 's her mom ?
- [ colleague ] Hey , you 're really leaving ? - Okay , sure . Don 't worry .
- Thanks . Have you seen my keys ? - [ colleague ] Did you tell Ms. Sung ?
How would I know where your keys are ?
- You should at least inform her . - Help me out , okay ? Cover for me , please .
- Thank you . Thanks . - Help you with what ?
- Thanks . - [ colleague ] Hey , Ronan !
Stop messing around !
[ eerie music ]
[ inaudible ]
[ Ronan ] It 's all right , don 't worry .
She 's in the car with me . We 're heading home now .
[ Ming ] Hey , drive safely , okay ?
I know you 're very busy .
And if Dodo needs anything ,
make sure you let me know . Okay ?
- [ Ronan sighs ] - [ Dodo ] I hate going to kindergarten .
Why is that ?
Because Chang Che-wei in my class keeps teasing me .
Why does he keep teasing you ?
He says that I 'm crazy .
Crazy ?
[ Ms. Hsia ] I heard Dodo bit someone at school .
How could this happen ?
She never did that at the foster home or our center .
I find this rather strange .
Are you in some kind of trouble ?
[ colleague ] You 're ridiculous .
How could you leave without informing the client ?
Did you know that Ms. Sung had to do her own makeup today ?
Listen , she 's looking for you now . You 're on your own .
I 've recovered . I 'm not scared anymore .
One , two , three . [ inhales ]
As long as I don 't worry , there 's no need to worry .
Yes . Right .
I have long recovered .
Amitābha . Amitābha .
Please deliver me from evil .
- Ami ... - [ robot vacuum ] Start cleaning .
[ vacuum whirs ]
[ robot vacuum ] Please move the base to a new location to start .
[ Dodo ] Come down !
Come down !
Mommy !
- What is it , Dodo ? - There 's a baddie .
- Who ? You said ... - Up there .
Nothing 's there .
Where 's ... where 's the baddie ?
It 's right up there ! Tell it to come down .
[ Ronan ] Okay .
All right , hang on , okay ?
Baddie !
Come down . Hurry up , baddie .
[ Dodo ] You have to lead it out by the hand .
Okay . Well ...
Have I got its hand now ?
[ Dodo ] Higher .
What about now ?
Higher . A bit higher .
Oh , have I got its hand now , huh ?
Have I ?
[ heavy breathing ]
Huh ?
You got it .
Okay .
Then ...
We 're going now . Okay ?
Baddie ?
Let 's go out and not stay in Dodo 's room .
Okay ?
[ Ronan clears throat ]
We 're going out now .
Come down !
Dodo , what are you doing ?
[ eerie music ]
CHIN CHIN KINDERGARTEN
[ teacher ] Slow down . Take care , don 't fall . Careful .
Actually , Dodo is very distracted in class .
- Ooh . - She 's not
really affecting the other students .
But she has this thing where she stares at the ceiling and talks to herself .
Her classmate said ,
that your daughter told them that she saw a faceless baddie ...
Principal , I 'm sorry . You see ...
Dodo told me something yesterday . She said ...
Kids , do you like the new toys we have ?
- [ classmate ] Yes . - Right , listen .
Dodo 's mom gave them to us .
We have to have manners . So , what do we say to Dodo 's mom ?
[ all ] Thank you !
Chen Dodo ,
I promise that I won 't call you crazy anymore .
From now on , I hope that we become good friends again
because your mom is very cool .
[ Ronan ] I hope that you stay good friends with Dodo , okay ?
Okay .
[ blood drips ]
[ exhales ]
[ grunts ]
CHIN CHIN KINDERGARTEN
[ principal ] Come on . Come on . Try and catch up with me .
Let 's play hide and seek .
Ready ?
Three , two , one . Run !
Dodo , where are you going to hide ? Where are you hiding ?
Dodo ?
[ principal gasps ]
[ slo-mo fearful music ]
Dodo .
What are you doing ?
I 'm playing with my toys .
Ooh .
Well , if you 're playing with them , then why are these dolls covered , huh ?
Because they don 't want to see the baddie .
Listen to Mommy , okay ?
You know , I used to see baddies too .
- Really , you did ? - Mm-hm .
[ in altered voice ] If you keep thinking about the monsters ,
the monsters will surely go and live inside your head .
Oh , no ! [ gasps ]
Doctor , what should I do then ? I 'm so scared .
Okay then , let Dr. Bunny tell you how .
Listen , if you 're feeling scared ,
all you have to do is think about
your three favorite things in the whole world .
Then , close your eyes and then say them out loud .
And after that , you won 't be scared anymore .
- I like three ... pineapples . - [ gasps ]
Oh , is that so ? Pineapple is your favorite ?
[ Ronan in altered voice ] How about me , don 't you like me anymore ?
Don 't you like me , Dodo ?
I like you too , bunny .
[ Ronan ] What about me ?
- Huh ? - [ imitates dog barking ]
- [ Ronan imitates dog barking ] - [ giggling ]
- Pineapple , bunny . - [ Ronan ] Pineapple , bunny .
[ both imitating dog barking ]
[ both giggling ]
Just think about these from now on whenever you 're scared .
Okay ?
Okay .
Okay , this is the last time .
Then straight to bed after . Hmm ?
[ Ronan ] If you don 't go to sleep ...
[ growls ] ... the monster will come and find you !
- Ooh , the monster will tickle ... - [ laughing ]
... you like this !
[ imitates roaring ]
- Mommy . - Hmm ?
Did you throw me away ,
because you were also scared of monsters , like me ?
[ in normal voice ] Mommy 's ...
Mommy 's not scared anymore .
Mm .
Go to sleep .
[ spooky music ]
LI RONAN
What is your name ?
Give it to me .
[ Ronan sniffles ]
What is your name ?
HOU-HO-XIU-YI , SI-SEI-WU-MA
Come .
Bow .
[ Great-aunt ] You must return
to worship Mother-Buddha every ten years .
After offering up your real name ,
remember , you cannot use it here anymore .
You mustn 't even think it in your mind .
[ snipping ]
[ reciting mantra ]
Mother-Buddha is happy .
Once the little girl growing in your tummy
has a name , you must offer it to Mother-Buddha too .
Understand ?
What ?
[ Yuan ] Come on , viewers , take a look at this .
This dinner was prepared by the great Chen clan .
Let 's try some now .
[ slurps ]
[ retches ] Fuck .
Come and eat .
- Why aren 't you eating ? - Huh ?
Have some .
I 'm not hungry .
I think it 's pretty good , come and try it . Hey , Ronan . Want to come and eat ?
I 'm already eating .
[ Yuan ] What 's this ? You got to be kidding me .
Come on , we 're ghostbusters .
Don 't tell me you actually believe that little girl ?
Why , who said anyone 's believing it ?
She believes it !
- [ Dom ] She 's just feeling unwell . - She does ! Look , she 's so nervous , okay ?
- Hey , bro , listen to me . - Can you ...
- [ Yuan ] She 's not possessed . - ... please cut it out ?
- [ Yuan ] She 's pregnant . - [ scoffs ]
[ scorns ]
Mind your own business .
I knew it .
[ exhales ] Dear viewers .
Take a good look .
This here is a playboy .
This is the face of a playboy .
[ exhales ]
- Are you okay ? - Yes , I 'm fine .
Are you sure ?
I 'm okay .
Fuck , stop being lovey-dovey .
Hurry up ! What are you doing ? It 's going to be over soon .
- [ Yuan ] Let 's go . - Oh .
- [ Yuan ] I 'm sorry . - Shh , shh . Go out , just go .
Slowly .
[ shushing ]
- [ clan ] Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - [ Yuan ] What are they worshipping ?
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi ... - Hou-ho-xiu-yi ...
- si-sei-wu-ma . - [ Yuan ] How strange .
Over there , the little girl . She 's over there .
- [ video flickers ] - [ Ronan ] Good , film her .
[ Yuan ] This is so weird .
- Fuck . - [ Dom ] What ?
[ Yuan ] I don 't know , wait . Just wait .
[ Yuan and Ronan gasping ]
[ Yuan ] She knows . Shit !
Did you three sneak out to play ?
[ both ] Yes .
[ Yuan ] Over there ?
Do you want to go somewhere fun ?
- [ Ronan ] Where ? - [ Yuan ] Sure .
Little girl , listen . It looks super fun over there .
Isn 't there a tunnel ?
[ chosen child ] You can 't go in there .
- [ Yuan ] Why ? - [ Ronan ] Where are we going ?
- Hey . Hey , hey , wait ! Little girl . - [ gate creaks open ]
[ creaks ]
You can 't come in .
[ Yuan ] She can , but why can 't I ?
I 'm sorry , but you just can 't .
[ Dom ] Oh , that 's fine , it 's okay .
What are you doing ?
Getting this . I can film with this .
[ chosen child ] Wait , for me here .
[ Ronan ] Huh ?
Wait ... [ hesitates ]
Where are you going , little girl ?
[ heavy breathing ]
[ dripping ]
[ Ronan ] What is this ?
[ eerie music ]
[ dripping continues ]
[ splutters ]
[ clinks , clanks ]
[ Ronan gasps , sighs ]
Come here .
- Look . - [ ribbits ]
Wait , what is that ?
Feed it .
- What , but ... - [ frog croaks ]
This ... this is hair .
Feed it .
[ sighs ]
Okay , hold on .
[ exhales ]
[ Ronan ] I 'm throwing it in now .
- [ clanks ] - [ Ronan gasps ]
GHOST BUSTERS WERE HERE
[ Yuan ] Hurry up , please . Come on .
[ in whispering voice ] Here , over here .
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - [ laughing ]
Hou-ho-xiu ...
What happened to your ear , huh ?
Mother-Buddha took it .
What does that mean ?
You see , I was chosen by the gods ,
so Mother-Buddha took my flesh in order to bless everyone .
[ clanks ]
- [ Ronan gasps ] - [ loud rattling ]
[ Ronan gasping ]
[ whimpers ]
[ chosen child ] Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
- [ Ronan grunts ] - Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - [ groans ]
- [ Granduncle ] What are you doing ? - [ Ronan gasps ]
Don 't you know that you can 't come in here ?
[ Ronan whimpers ]
- One , two , three ! - [ Ronan ] One , two , three !
- [ both giggling ] - Whoo !
Awesome !
Today is Dodo 's birthday .
Wow , why do you keep getting shorter , huh ?
♪ There was once a little princess ♪
♪ Flying in the sky way up high ♪
♪ The little princess Stops on a white cloud ♪
♪ Then keeps flying by ♪
♪ She is in the castle in the sky ♪
♪ Living oh so fine ♪
[ inhales , blows air ]
[ Ronan ] Wow ! Amazing !
- Mom , come here . - Hmm ?
Look at him .
[ Ronan ] You like him ?
[ Dodo ] It 's Woofy .
[ Ronan ] That 's Woofy ? Is he Woofy ?
- [ barks ] - Woofy .
Woofy ?
Look at Woofy .
Please tell me , Mommy , when can we bring Woofy home ?
Well ...
We 'll bring him home when you 're all grown up
and can look after him . Otherwise , no one will take care of him .
- Okay ? - [ scoffs ]
Come on , have some , okay ?
Hmm ? Aah .
Aah ...
Is it delicious ?
It 's okay .
Hey little girl , what are you filming ?
[ Dodo ] It 's a birthday video .
- Thank you . - [ Ronan ] Why don 't we ...
I have some questions about the house .
Okay , sure . Dodo , wait for me here .
I 'll go inside and I 'll be right back . Okay ? Hmm ?
[ agent ] Well , the Buddha statues on the top floor ...
Do you still want them ?
- I think they 're kind of scary . - [ Dodo clicks tongue ]
[ Ronan ] Uh ... I 'll get someone to take care of that .
Okay . I think some buyers would , you know ... Some would care about these things , yes .
[ Dodo ] Hmm ?
Where should I go ?
Huh ? What is it ?
[ loud banging , creaks ]
[ eerie music ]
[ Dodo ] Yes .
[ tense music ]
Is it down there ?
[ tense music continues ]
And then what ?
Okay .
[ banging ]
[ dog barking in distance ]
[ footsteps ]
[ clinks ]
[ percussive music ]
[ thuds ]
Now , what do I do ?
Where do I go ?
[ percussive music continues ]
[ lock clicks ]
Yes ?
[ door creaks ]
- [ Dodo giggles ] - [ camera focus whirs ]
[ Dodo ] Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
[ Dodo laughs ]
[ door creaks ]
[ indistinct chatter on video ]
[ Ronan ] Dodo !
Chen Le-tung , what are you doing ?
[ Ronan groans ]
[ pants ]
Didn 't I tell you to stay right there , Dodo ?
I told you to wait . Why didn 't you listen to me ? Why ?
[ rapid panting ]
Do ... Dodo !
Dodo , what 's the matter ? Dodo !
[ panting ]
[ Ming ] She was fine when I saw her a few days ago .
What the doctor means is ...
that Dodo 's hemiparesis might be brain-induced ?
[ heavy breathing ]
[ gasps ] Oh , by the way ...
Here . Take it .
You see , a few days ago ,
Ms. Hsia got this for Dodo , it 's from the temple .
Dodo 's name is inside it .
- And hopefully , it will keep her safe . - I don 't want it .
Why ...
Why did you give me that ?
I ... I didn 't say I wanted it .
[ host ] Now , the teacher is using a different tool ,
so we can make changes and adjustments to the shape .
And right now , as you can see him doing ,
the teacher is using the digging and kneading method .
Look at his technique carefully . In order for him to change the shape ,
the raw material must be very soft .
That means the temperature must be very high .
So , what would happen if the temperature drops ?
Obviously , the work will be hard ,
and there 's no way to shape the raw material .
In the process of creation , you must also pay close attention to ...
- [ sizzles ] - [ crowd screaming ]
[ Yuan ] What ? But we 're already here .
It doesn 't matter . Go home tomorrow morning .
Granduncle , but it 's so far from here .
- [ door closing shut ] - [ Yuan ] Granduncle !
Shit , they locked the door .
- Fuck , seriously ? - I think they locked us in .
[ door rattles ]
- [ Dom ] Hey ! - [ bangs on door ]
- [ Yuan ] Let us out ! - Why did you lock the door ?
- [ Dom ] Hey ! - [ door rattles ]
[ Dom ] Do you have any tools ?
- [ Yuan ] Oh , shit . - Maybe there 's something here we can use ?
[ camera beeps ]
- [ Yuan ] Got it ? - [ lock clicks ]
I think so .
[ Yuan ] Try it .
[ door rattles , thuds ]
It 's open ! Okay , come on , let 's go .
- [ Dom ] Hey , wait . - [ Yuan ] I can 't believe they locked us in .
- Shit . - [ Dom ] Hey , Yuan .
What ?
Look at her .
[ Yuan ] How are you feeling ? Are you okay ?
[ sighs ]
- I 'm okay . - See , she 's okay .
Are you sure ?
[ grunts ]
I 'm not sure where the little girl went . Let 's take a look .
Yes , let 's check on her . Hurry , come on .
[ Yuan ] Okay . Dear viewers .
The Ghost Busters are heading to the forbidden place .
- The infamous place you must not go to . - [ chicken cackles ]
[ Yuan ] Film the barrier talisman . Film it quickly .
Yeah . Yeah , that 's it .
Wow ! Look at this barrier talisman .
It 's terrifying .
Let 's go .
[ Ronan retching ]
[ Yuan ] Hey . What 's wrong now ?
[ retching , vomits ]
Oh . [ chuckles ]
Dear viewers .
Up next ,
the moment you 've been waiting for . We 'll be heading into
the Chen clan 's " tunnel you must not enter . "
- [ panting ] - Hey .
- [ exhales ] - Are you really pregnant ?
What 's the matter ? Are you scared ?
- [ grunts ] - No , I 'm not scared .
What else could it be ?
Let 's name her Chen Le-tung .
- What ? - [ Yuan ] Fuck !
You 're being lovey-dovey again .
- [ Dom ] No , we 're not . - Then what are you doing ?
[ Dom ] She 's not feeling well .
- [ Yuan ] You idiots , hurry up ! - Okay !
- [ Yuan ] Fuck ! Fuck ! Fuck ! - [ Ronan ] What ? What 's wrong ?
- [ Dom ] What is it ? - Turn off the flashlight . Hurry !
- [ Ronan ] What ? - Turn it off first . Hurry .
[ Dom ] Come on . Hurry this way . Follow me .
Turn off the flashlight . Hurry , hurry , hurry !
[ Ronan ] I 'm turning it off . It 's off .
[ woman vocalizing screams ]
[ cymbals beat ]
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei ... - Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei ...
[ camera beeps off ]
I watched it .
[ Dr. Wu ] What exactly are you afraid of ?
Are you afraid of not being forgiven ?
Or are you afraid that even you can 't forgive yourself ?
One , two , three , go .
[ grunts ]
It 's okay .
Are you afraid of this curse , or that you 're going crazy again ?
Don 't think . Don 't think about anything , then I 'll win .
Yes , I just need to do it .
Don 't think .
Don 't think . Don 't think .
Some people see a fallen chair and say it 's a ghost .
- [ splutters ] - [ Ronan gasping ]
What the hell ?
You told me you 're not afraid of monsters anymore .
You said so yourself !
But others would see a fallen chair and say that it 's ...
a miracle from God .
[ Ronan ] Dodo .
Don 't be scared , okay ?
[ Dr. Wu ] The world is as you choose to see it .
I can 't give you an answer .
Oh , gosh . This head looks so tasty . [ imitates chomping ]
[ Dr. Wu ] How you view the world
can truly bring about tiny changes to it .
This is very important . I have a document here for you to sign .
It mainly says that the court has revoked your custody rights .
Go ahead . Just sign here .
- We need your cooperation here . - No , I cannot sign it .
Please consider this carefully , this is a notice from the court .
You have no choice on the matter .
- You are just being notified . - [ sobbing ]
[ Dr. Wu ] I do not know
if ghosts or gods
really do exist .
[ Dr. Wu ] But what I am certain of
is that you decide
how your world is shaped .
[ somber music ]
[ Ronan ] Dodo . Listen , I 'm going up to get something .
I 'll be back real quick .
Where are we going , Mommy ?
- Do you trust your Mommy ? - Mm .
Good .
- [ indistinct chatter on radio ] - [ indistinct chatter ]
[ police siren blares ]
[ knocks on window ]
Dodo ?
Hi , Dodo .
Open this window for daddy .
[ pants ]
Dodo .
Where 's your mom ?
My mom went upstairs .
Your mom is upstairs ?
Did your mom ...
Did your mom say where you 're going ?
[ exhales ]
[ sighs ]
Dodo .
Do you want to go back to my place ?
Yes , dad .
Yes ? Okay , then let 's go back home .
[ somber music ]
What 's the matter ?
If we go , then what about Mom ?
[ exhales ]
[ knocks on window ]
Open the door . Hurry , please .
Open up ! Come on !
- [ knocking continues ] - Please !
Open the door .
Open the door !
Get in . Get in !
[ woman 1 ] She 's over there .
That 's her . That 's her !
[ guard 1 ] Stay there !
- Wait , miss ! - [ woman 2 ] Stop the car .
- [ guard 2 ] Pull over ! Hurry to the front . - Please stop !
- [ woman 2 ] Miss , please ! - [ woman 1 ] Stop the car !
[ guard 1 ] Stop !
- [ guard 2 ] Stop the car ! Hey ! - [ car engine revs ]
[ guard 3 ] Hey ! Wait !
[ Yuan ] Hurry , hurry , hurry ! Over here .
[ Ronan ] What , what is it ?
- Fuck , it 's that little girl . - [ Ronan ] What 's going on ?
- Little girl ? - [ Dom ] Let 's take her down first .
- [ Ronan 's heavy breathing ] - [ Dom pants ]
- Little girl . - [ gasping ]
- Little girl , wake up . - [ Yuan ] Dear viewers .
This must be the Chen family 's
" tunnel that you must not enter . "
HOU-HO-XIU-YI
Yes , this must be it .
How is she ?
- [ Yuan ] A pig 's head . - [ goat bleats ]
There 's a goat .
[ Ronan ] Little girl , can you hear my voice ?
Okay , this is it . Let 's go in .
- Yuan . Let 's forget it . - What ?
- Huh ? - I have a bad feeling about this .
- How many times are you going to do this ? - [ Ronan ] Should we ...
- take her down to see a doctor first . - Shit ! Are you insane ?
Fuck , motherfucker !
- [ Dom ] Hey . - [ Yuan ] You do this every time .
- Ronan 's not feeling well . Cut it out . - [ Yuan ] Fuck !
- Are you stupid ? Fucking asshole . - [ Ronan ] Yuan .
- [ Dom ] Chen Chen-yuan ! - [ glass breaking , thuds ]
Chen Chen-yuan !
[ clanks ]
[ wind blows ]
- [ wailing ] - [ wind rustles ]
[ Ronan ] Did you hear something ?
- What 's that sound ? - [ disembodied voices ]
[ child crying ]
Is that a child crying ?
[ child crying continues ]
Yuan .
Are you sure you want to go in ?
[ Ronan ] But wait ...
[ grunts ]
... what if there are other children in there ?
- Let 's go . - Hey .
[ sighs ]
[ exhales ]
What ?
Stay here and look after her .
- I 'm going in with Yuan . - But , what if ...
Let 's go .
[ Dom sighs ]
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
THE PLACE YOU MUST NOT ENTER
- [ chosen child groans ] - [ Ronan ] What 's the matter ?
Are you okay ?
- [ chosen child continues to groan ] - Hey !
[ grunts , heavy breathing ]
[ groans ]
[ grunts ]
What 's going on ?
- [ Yuan screams ] - Dom !
- [ Ronan shrieks ] - [ screaming continues ]
Where are you going ? Yuan !
Yuan !
Where are you going ?
Chen Chen-yuan ! [ sobbing ]
[ Ronan whimpers ] Dom .
[ sobs ] What should I do ?
- [ thuds ] - Huh ?
- [ thuds ] - [ Ronan gasps ]
[ eerie music ]
[ inaudible ]
[ inaudible chatter ]
[ rumbles ]
[ Ronan 's shaky breathing ]
- [ Yuan ] Don 't ask . - [ gasping ]
[ bleats ]
[ Yuan ] Don 't ask !
[ gasping ]
[ Ronan ] Yuan .
[ whimpers ]
[ heavy breathing , pants ]
Yuan .
- [ screams ] - [ glass breaking ]
[ grunts ]
- [ Yuan ] Don 't ask ! - [ whimpers ]
[ shaky breathing , pants ]
Yuan .
[ dog barking ]
[ disembodied voices ]
- [ whimpers ] - [ camera clicks ]
[ fire crackles ]
[ Ronan gasping ]
[ Yuan ] Don 't ask !
[ whimpers ]
Don 't ask .
[ gasping ]
[ Ronan screams ]
[ screams , groans ]
- So , itchy . My teeth . - [ Ronan 's heavy breathing ]
- My teeth . - Yuan ...
My teeth !
- [ Yuan screams ] - Yuan !
[ both screaming ]
[ door closes ]
[ groans , grunts ]
[ screams , whimpers ]
[ yelps , panting ]
- [ muffled screaming ] - [ Ronan yelps ]
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
[ Yuan ] Don 't ask !
- [ thuds ] - [ Ronan whimpers ]
[ screams ]
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - [ Ronan continues to scream ]
[ shaky breathing ]
[ Ming ] How much further is the temple ?
[ Ronan ] It should be close . I haven 't been there for a long time .
What is that ?
Did you see it ?
[ percussive music ]
[ Ronan ] Is that a person ?
[ gasping ]
How is this possible ?
[ eerie music ]
[ reverse alarm beeps ]
[ engine revs ]
- [ engine sputters ] - [ gasping ]
Hey .
What 's going on ?
- How could this happen ? - [ engine sputters ]
[ engine continues to sputter ]
- [ rustling ] - [ Ronan 's heavy breathing ]
[ engine sputters ]
Something 's wrong .
What is it ?
What are you doing ?
It 's nothing .
- [ banging ] - [ both screaming ]
[ reporter ] A shocking gas explosion happened at a psychiatric treatment clinic
in Yuexiang Road Section 3 .
- In the toilet ... - [ disembodied voice ]
[ loud static ]
... hanging corpse .
The victim is the person-in-charge , Dr. Wu Yu-ching .
- The cause of the fire remains unclear ... - [ Ming grunts ]
- [ engine sputters ] - Come on , start !
[ banging continues ]
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
Mommy , I 'm scared .
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
- Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma . - [ panting ]
- [ shaky breathing ] - [ panting continues ]
It 's okay . It 's okay .
VANQUISH DEMONS , CATCH GHOSTS , ELIMINATE EVIL SPIRITS
[ grunts ] What should come will come .
[ clicks tongue ]
Such as fate .
[ reciting mantra ]
What exactly is in the camera ?
[ reciting mantra continues ]
[ Madam Ching ] You have to remember and this is important .
Don 't let the child eat anything for seven days straight .
[ Ronan ] Seven days ! But how can a child not eat for so long ?
The master and I are putting our lives on the line here .
[ scoffs ] If you can 't do that ,
let 's just end this right now and stop this .
We have to set up the altar .
Remember you must not let her eat .
Come back in seven days .
[ Ronan ] Could you please tell me ,
how does it feel to raise a child into adulthood ?
[ Ming clicks tongue ] As you know , it 's a foster home . So ...
children , they tend to come and go .
[ Ming inhales ]
I 've never really raised a child into an adult , so ...
I want to know the answer to that too .
What it feels like to raise a child into adulthood .
[ Ming ] Dodo .
Tell me , you like your Mommy , huh ?
Mm .
But don 't you think that she 's very strange ?
Yes , but she 's still my Mommy .
[ sighs ]
[ hesitates ]
[ shaky breathing ]
[ Ronan ] Ming , don 't you have your own children ?
Let 's skip this question .
Okay .
Let 's talk about Dodo .
[ inaudible ]
[ somber music ]
[ inaudible chatter ]
I TOOK THE VIDEO CAMERA , I 'LL FIND OUT WHAT REALLY HAPPENED
I WANT TO KNOW HOW IT FEELS LIKE TO BE A REAL DAD
[ kids laughing in distance ]
[ Ronan ] Dodo .
Have you flown a kite before ?
Not yet .
Sir .
How much is this kite at the front ?
[ store clerk ] Oh , that 's not for sale . A customer ordered it .
The bubble blower is better , yeah .
She can blow on it while sitting down . She 's in a wheelchair anyway .
- Hmm , no , that 's okay . - The bubble blower is nice .
- No , it 's fine . - Okay .
[ Dodo ] Mommy , it 's bad to steal things , right ?
[ Ronan ] We 'll return it later so we won 't be bad . Hmm ?
[ somber music ]
I hope she 's happy when she remembers our time together .
[ somber music continues ]
[ Dodo grunts ]
[ Ronan ] Dodo ?
Huh ?
Why are you all sweaty ?
Do you feel really hot ?
Let 's go .
- Bunny . - Come on , bunny .
We 're almost at the hospital . Okay ?
Hold on a little longer .
Hello , is anybody there ? [ knocks ]
LAI HSIEN-CHUNG 'S CLINIC
Is there anybody there ?
Come on ...
[ doctor ] Hang on . Hang on , hang on !
Please take a look at her . It won 't take long , it will be very quick .
[ whimpers ]
Oh , dear ! She needs an injection .
The antipyretic will have side effects on an empty stomach .
Feed her then come back .
But doctor ... must she really eat ?
She can 't be injected with it otherwise . Don 't you get it ?
- Hurry up ! Hurry ! - Okay .
- I 'll wait for you . Move . - [ whimpers ]
Okay , okay .
HOW TO ADMINISTER A DRIP ?
HOW TO ADMINISTER A DRIP AT HOME ? INTRAVENOUS METHOD
[ inhales , exhales ]
[ Ronan ] Today marks the third day .
Her legs have become wrinkly .
I think they 're atrophying .
I wonder if I hadn 't brought her home ,
would she still turn out this way ?
[ heavy breathing ]
[ Dodo grunts ]
I 'm so hungry .
Let 's get rid of this , okay ?
- Mm . - I 'll take it out .
[ Dodo groans ]
[ in weak voice ] On my birthday ...
We had such a big cake .
[ in normal voice ] Is this for Mommy ?
Mm .
[ in strained voice ] Then I 'll eat it .
[ Dodo ] Don 't cry .
[ sniffles ]
[ Dodo ] All you need to do is think of your three favorite things
and you won 't be scared anymore .
Mm .
[ sniffles ]
[ sobbing ]
[ chomps , sniffling ]
[ sobs ]
Keep the change .
Here .
Ah .
Mmm .
It 's so sweet .
[ heavy breathing ]
What do I do ?
[ whimpers ]
THE VIDEO CLIP OF THE TUNNEL
[ Ming ] This video camera isn 't broken , the file was just destroyed .
Then I found a repairing software on an international website .
[ scoffs ]
But the repair progress of the tunnel clip keeps failing .
This is strange but the more of this video I watch ...
[ grunts ] ... the more unwell I feel .
- [ grunts ] - [ clinks ]
[ sniffles , exhales ]
Could this be a curse ?
[ Ming ] So ...
Okay , the hand gesture they do
is like a modified version of Bafangtian in Tantric Buddhism .
The difference is
if Bafangtian gesture means to " collect blessing . "
This one 's ending gesture is completely in the opposite direction .
So , what does it mean ?
To spread ...
Spread it ?
[ camera beeps ]
[ grunts ]
[ Ming ] In this image captured on the video ,
there are similar temples all around it .
There 's a goat on top of that temple .
So , I asked a few of my theologian friends .
And they told me .
This kind of twisted text looks like a Brahmic script
used to record Buddhist scriptures in ancient India .
Then I researched online later on .
SHI KONG-YUN
There 's a Tantric Buddhist monk in Yunnan who lives in seclusion .
He 's one of the last remaining people
who can translate ancient Buddhist scriptures .
So ...
I 'm thinking that if I can go there
and find him ,
maybe I 'll get an answer .
[ camera beeps ]
[ flight attendant ] Ladies and gentlemen , you 're arriving at
Xishuangbanna Gasa International Airport .
[ door creaks open ]
[ monk speaks in Yunnan dialect ]
[ chimes ]
[ Ming in English ] This should be the place .
[ speaks in Yunnan dialect ]
[ in English ] I think he 's telling me to wait right here .
[ camera beeps ]
Listen carefully ,
I 've forwarded you the video of the Yunnan monk .
It explains the origins of the disciples and the meaning
of ... of the incantation .
The ... [ gasps ]
[ shivers ]
The video clip of the tunnel has finally been repaired .
But I won 't send it to you anymore .
I 'm sorry .
I was the one who reported your inadequacy to the Social Affairs Bureau .
Because I didn 't trust you .
I also thought it was unfair to me .
I 'm sorry .
If something untoward happens to me ,
I hope you can let Dodo know that ,
that even though I can never have ...
my very own children biologically ...
I 'm very happy that ...
Dodo was willing to call me Dad .
[ video whirs ]
Hsieh Chi-ming .
[ thuds ]
Hsieh ...
Hsieh Chi-ming .
[ gasping ]
[ phone chimes ]
FROM MING ATTACHMENT : INSIDE THE TUNNEL
- [ Dodo ] Ouch , it hurts ... - [ phone continues chiming ]
What hurts ?
My hand ...
Your hand ?
Let me see .
[ Ronan gasps ]
[ gasps ]
[ whimpers ]
[ exhales ]
Come on .
Spit out the pineapple , okay ?
Okay , here we go .
[ Dodo retches , grunts ]
- [ vomits ] - Okay , very good .
- One more time . One more time , okay ? - [ Dodo coughs ]
- One more time , come on . - [ vomiting continues ]
[ Ronan ] One , two , three .
[ Dodo retches , vomits ]
[ gasping , whimpers ]
[ eerie music ]
[ Ronan 's shaky breathing ]
[ Ronan ] Master Ching !
[ panting ]
Master Ching .
Madam Ching !
[ panting continues ]
- [ foreboding music ] - [ gasps ]
Master Ching ...
[ gasping ]
[ Madam Ching ] Did you let the child eat ?
Madam Ching .
Listen , child .
Let me tell you .
When your mother was pregnant with you ,
she was going to offer you to the gods .
[ gasps ]
[ trickles , drips ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ Madam Ching groans ]
[ groans ]
[ groans , grunts ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ spooky music ]
- [ thuds ] - [ screams ]
- [ rattles ] - [ whimpers ]
[ gasping ]
[ disembodied voices ]
[ Ronan whimpers , pants ]
[ whimpers ]
- [ shrieks ] - [ Ronan screams ]
[ whimpers , sobs ]
Dodo .
[ gasps ] Dodo !
[ thuds ]
[ in hoarse voice ] Dodo !
[ Ronan ] Do you ...
Do you believe in such things as blessings ?
My name is Li Ronan .
Six years ago , I violated a terrifying taboo .
HOU-HO-XIU-YI , SI-SEI-WU-MA
[ Ronan ] Help me .
Please recite this with me .
Doing it in your mind is fine too .
HOU-HO-XIU-YI , SI-SEI-WU-MA
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
[ Ronan ] Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
[ inaudible ]
[ speaks in Yunnan ]
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma is ...
[ in English ] The Yunnan monk says that ,
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma
is actually an ancient religious blessing .
This religion spread from Southeast Asia to Yunnan ,
and to where Dom 's family is .
The deity worshiped by their ancestors is called Dahei Mother-Buddha .
It 's a malicious deity .
So ...
they 've inherited bad karma from generation to generation .
They must use this incantation in order to receive blessings .
Therefore , if a lot of people chanted ,
the power of blessing will be gathered
and it will protect the person who chants it .
[ indistinct chanting ]
The child 's breathing and pulse have stabilized for now .
That 's good news regarding her condition .
But we noticed that she has severe dehydration
and she suffers from malnutrition .
Bacterial infection has already spread across her entire body .
I am arranging for her to be monitored further in the ICU .
- Thank you , doctor . - But Ms. Li ,
things are far from being good .
You need to be prepared for the worst .
[ sniffles , whimpers ]
[ sobs ]
INSIDE THE TUNNEL.MOV
PLAY
[ eerie music ]
A naked girl around junior high age
was discovered lying naked in an empty lot beside a hospital
shown to be wearing only her undergarments .
What 's strange is that runes were written all over her body .
[ Ronan ] Dodo , Mommy 's here . Open your eyes and look at me , okay ?
[ sobs ] Dodo ?
Right now , she 's still unconscious .
So , now ... now what ? What do we do ?
[ Ronan ] What now ?
Please , calm down .
She 's not in a good condition ,
but we will continue monitoring her .
By the way , didn 't she mention something earlier ?
Something like pineapple bun ...
Pineapple bunny .
It 's probably a doll .
[ inaudible ]
[ somber music ]
[ inaudible crying ]
- Mommy . - Hmm ?
Did you throw me away
because you were also scared of monsters , like me ?
[ Ronan ] Mommy 's ...
Mommy 's not scared anymore .
[ monitor beeps ]
[ Ronan exhales ]
[ shaky breathing ]
I 'm about to show you
the video when we violated the taboo six years ago .
[ Dom ] This way .
- Hey , Yuan . Yuan ! - [ Yuan ] Hmm ?
Look at this .
[ Yuan ] Hey , don 't touch it .
[ Dom ] I 'll just take a look .
MISFORTUNE AND BLESSING DEPEND ON EACH OTHER
[ disembodied voice ]
[ Yuan ] The sound is coming from there .
[ pants ]
[ Yuan ] Hey , there 's a mirror over there .
[ heavy breathing ]
Hey , watch your step .
[ bat screeching ]
[ Yuan ] There are so many mirrors here too .
[ camera whirs ]
Let 's keep going .
[ Yuan ] Is that a door ?
[ Dom ] I don 't know .
[ Dom ] What ?
[ Yuan ] I 'm looking .
[ heavy breathing ]
[ disembodied voice ]
Did you hear that ?
[ disembodied voice continues ]
Let 's move it aside .
SI-SEI-WU-MA
[ Dom ] Careful .
[ creaks , thuds ]
There 's another mirror behind it .
[ Dom ] Let 's go .
Are we going in ?
Look at this .
[ Yuan ] I filmed the same thing earlier .
[ camera whirs ]
[ Yuan ] Hair .
[ Dom ] Hey .
Don 't touch it .
There 's another one .
[ whirs ]
Hey , come over here .
What the hell is this ?
- Teeth . - [ Dom ] Huh ?
- [ disembodied voice ] - Hey , listen .
You hear that ?
[ gasps ]
That sound .
[ disembodied voice continues ]
Take a look over there .
[ foreboding music ]
There .
[ camera whirs ]
[ Yuan ] Hey .
Forget about it . Let 's go back .
[ Dom ] It 's okay .
[ Yuan ] Is anything there ?
If not , let 's go .
- [ disembodied voice ] - What are you doing ?
- [ disembodied voice continues ] - [ gasps ]
- The sound . - What are you doing ?
I 'll uncover it . Hold this for me . Hurry up .
[ heavy breathing ]
[ Yuan ] Dom .
What is it , Dom ?
[ Dom ] What 's my name ?
[ Yuan ] Dom .
Chen Li-tung !
[ gasps ] Hey !
What are you doing ?
What are you doing ? Hey !
Chen Li-tung , that 's enough !
What are you doing ? Don 't scare me like this .
Don 't scare me ! What are you doing ?
- Hurry ! Let 's get out of here ! - [ disembodied voices ]
Don 't scare me ! Hurry , let 's go !
[ grunts , whimpers ]
Dom ! Get up , hurry !
[ disembodied voices continue ]
Let 's go !
Dom , let 's go !
Dom , come on . Let 's go !
- Let 's go ! - [ crashing ]
[ grunts ] Dom . Dom !
Dom . Dom !
[ glass breaking ]
Dom !
- [ Yuan screams ] - [ glass breaking ]
- No ! - [ glass breaking continues ]
- [ Yuan panting ] - [ camera whirs ]
Dom ?
Dom .
Where are you , Dom ?
[ whimpers ]
[ clanks ]
[ growls ]
[ whizzing ]
[ Yuan gasps ]
Dom ?
[ clanks ]
[ heavy breathing , panting ]
Dom ?
[ rapid panting ]
- [ thuds ] - Huh ?
[ whimpers ]
[ groans ]
[ whimpers , pants ]
[ Dom croaks ]
[ thuds ]
Dom , what are you doing ?
Dom ?
- [ thuds ] - [ gasping ]
Dom , what are you doing ?
Dom !
Dom .
[ whimpers ]
- [ roars ] - [ screams ]
[ screaming continues ]
Help !
[ distorted screaming ]
They say that
the moment you set your eyes on your child
you will instantly feel like a mother .
But I didn 't .
I was just so scared .
[ Ronan ] I 'm still scared now .
I don 't know if I 'm very selfish .
CHEN LE-TUNG
I don 't know if I only want to be good to you
because of the guilt I 'm feeling .
[ Ronan ] I don 't even know how it was that I fell in love with you .
Did I fall in love with you while watching you sleep ?
Or was it when you were crying ?
Is that love ?
[ dog whimpers ]
You didn 't have a choice , right ?
You could have been in a better place .
[ Ronan ] You could 've been fine .
Forgive me .
Dodo .
[ somber music ]
I 'm sorry .
Mommy won 't hurt you anymore .
Listen , if you wake up ,
can you promise me ...
to forget your name ?
And forget me .
From now on ,
if you 're happy ,
then laugh out loud .
And when you walk , walk properly with big , big strides .
And if ever you see food that you like , take big , big mouthfuls and grow plump .
[ somber music continues ]
Promise Mom .
When you open your eyes every day ,
you have to be happier than others .
[ Ronan pants ]
[ grunts ]
GHOST BUSTERS WERE HERE
[ trickling ]
[ grunts , pants ]
[ grunts ]
[ eerie music ]
[ camera whirs ]
[ glass breaking ]
[ grunts ]
[ clanks ]
[ sighs ]
[ pants ]
[ grunts , pants ]
[ groans , pants ]
[ exhales , sniffles ]
[ camera whirs ]
[ inhales , exhales ]
[ exhales ]
Do you still remember the incantation ?
And if you can , please ,
recite it with me in your mind again .
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
Look .
This is the full translation from the Yunnan monk .
Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma .
[ dings ]
[ Ronan ] Forgive me .
I lied to you .
If you 're not willing to keep watching ,
then do this . Please think of your three favorite things .
From now on ,
please close your eyes .
[ in Yunnan ] Actually , " Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma " ,
the incantation ,
is not a blessing .
It 's a Minnan dialect saying that " misfortune and blessing
depend on one another , death and life lies in the name . "
Reciting it means ,
" I wish to share in this curse and offer up my name . "
As for the symbol ,
it 's a spell for diffusing Mother-Buddha 's curse onto strangers .
The more people bearing the curse , the more diluted it becomes .
The deeper you look , the heavier the burden .
The Mother-Buddha 's face is the heart of the curse .
That 's why they cover it up and never look at it .
[ translator in English ] Ms. Li ,
what the master means is that . Hou-ho-xiu-yi , si-sei-wu-ma ...
I 'm sorry .
I 'm aware that some things should not be seen .
But this is really the only way I can save my daughter .
If I can manipulate more people to see this video and this symbol ,
then perhaps her curse will be lessened .
[ foreboding music ]
If possible ,
I really wish that you weren 't my child .
[ sobs ]
Because I 'm not a good mother .
[ sniffles ]
Because ...
I really ...
really wish you can open your eyes every day .
[ sniffles ]
And be very happy .
[ inhales ]
[ sniffles , whimpers ]
[ exhales ]
What is your name ?
[ screeching ]
[ disembodied voices ]
[ thuds ]
Our beautiful home is so far away .
But it 's okay . We can catch a bus .
But there are no buses heading to our castle .
Our castle was blown away by bubbles .
Pretty bubbles !
[ closing theme music ]